A Guide to the Huddle Family Papers, 1796-1953
Special Collections, Kegley Library, Wytheville Community College
Special Collections, Kegley Library, Wytheville Community College
Huddle Family Papers 1796-1953.
Special Collections, Kegley Library
1997.8
96 folders..
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Beverly Repass Hoch in 1987 and 1997.
Accruals
The donor gave additional materials in 2000 (James Layfayette Buck letters)and 2006 (account ledgers and miscelleneous Black Lick Township papers). The donor also gave additionalcorrespondence in 2008.
Biographical Information
Born on 16 May 1768 in Shenandoah County, Virginia, Henry Huddle was the son of John Huddle and Elizabeth Piper Huddle. After her first husband died, Elizabeth Huddle married Peter Spangler Jr. and moved to Wythe County. At age twenty-eight, Henry Huddle purchased 200 acres in the Kimberling section of the young countty along a tributary of Reed Creek which eventually was named Huddle Branch. Neighbors of Henry and his wife Magdalene Kimberling Huddle (1770-1845) included the Cassell family, Cook family, Dutton family, Kimberling family, Reusch family, and Snavely family. As his neighbors, Huddle depended upon his farm for his livelihood. According to local memory, Huddle also built pie safes.
Henry and Magdalene Huddle raised eight daughters and three sons. Henry Huddle died on 14 December 1846 and Magdalene died on 27 January 1845. Both are buried in the Kimberling Church cemetery.
Their son Jonas, born on 17 July 1806, continued to farm and live at the family home. On 23 May 1833, he married Elizabeth Brown (1806-1885). Jonas not only farmed but also served as justice of the peace and as the Kimberling Church Sunday school superintendent. Jonas Huddle also served as an Overseer of the Poor and often helped settle estates for various families.
Jonas Huddle and Elizabeth Huddle had five girls and three sons. Jonas died on 24 May 1881 and Elizabeth died on 24 April 1885. Both are buried in the Kimberling Church cemetery.
Their youngest son, Isaac Newton Huddle, was born on 7 May 1849. Isaac was a farmer but also participated in local politics, serving on the Wythe County Board of Supervisors and on the Black Lick Township Board. Isaac also served as clerk for the Black Lick Township Board from 1871 to 1875. On 3 October 1872 he married Sarah Jane Steffey (1849-1936). Isaac Huddle and Sarah Huddle raised two daughters, Minnie Elizabeth neff (married A. Oden Neff) and Emma Katharine Copenhaver (married Edgar P. Copenhaver). Isaac Huddle died on 17 February 1924 and his wife Sarah Huddle dield on 24 Apr8il 1936; both are buried in Kimberling Church cemetery.
Scope and Content
The Huddle Family Papers are arranged in six series. Series I, Correspondence (1872-1912) includes letters to Isaac Newton Huddle and John Huddle involving financial transactions.
Valuable information regarding early financial transactions in Wythe County may be found in Series II, Financial Records (1807-1953). Account books belonging to Henry Huddle, his son Jonas Huddle, and his grandson Isaac Newton Huddle combined with receipts and tax receipts provide researchers a glimpse into the personal and professional business of the Huddle family. Also included in this series are financial records involving the estates of Adam Snaffle and David Musser.
Series III, Land Records (1796-1896), includes several early deeds transferring property purchased by the Huddle family. The earliest deed recrods the purchase of Henry Huddle in 1796 of 200 acres along Huddle Branch from Jacob Tobler. Other records in this series include portions of surveys.
Information regarding nineteenth century education practices may be found in Series IV, Education Records (1812-1882). Several notesbooks used by James E. Poe and Jonas Huddle illustrate instructional methods in penmanship and arithmetic. Two compositions by Isaac Newton Huddle and an arithmetic textbook, Caldwell's Practical Arithmetic, complete this series.
Series VI, Miscellaneous Records (1868-1871) include an article by Jonas Huddle on the Sluss family massacre, a poem, and a hand-drawn map of Virginia. Brochures from the Pitts Agricultural Works, Richmond Hair Dye Company, Dickie's Poultry Powder Company, and the Golding Printing Press Company, and a flyer for the Louisville, St. Louis and Chicago railroad schedule complete this series.
Series VI, Black Lick Township Records (1870-1875) documents the formation and activities of Black Lick Township from 1870 to 1875. Isaac Newton Huddle served as clerk for the Township from 1871 to 1875. The Township records were found in the Huddle home in the 1980s. Materails include claims, tax receipts, and lsits of delinquent taxpayers. Also included are records of the Overseers of the Roads. Appointed by the Township Board, each overseer was responsible for road construction and maintenance in his district. Records of the Overseers of the Poor are also found in this series. These citizens coordinated efforts to provide medical care, room and board for poorer residents of the Township.
An important component of this series is the official order book of the Township Board. Here are recorded transactions of the Board including meetings, claims allowed, listings of Overseers of the Roads and the Poor, listings of road hands, and levying and collection of taxes.
Series VII contains correspondence of James Lafayette Buck, a Mt. Airy, Virginia, native to Isaac Newton Huddle. Buck attended Roanoke College and the Salem Lutheran Seminary in Salem, Virginia. The letters date from 1870 to 1878. Beverly Repass Hoch transcribed and annotated the letters; a copy may be found in the Kegley Library.
Series VIII, 2006 Addendum, contains two account ledgers and several loose papers relating to Black Lick Township.
Contents List
- Correspondence 1866-1912., 8 folders.
  - Folder 1. Correspondence. 1871-1912., 3 items.
    - Letter. Cousin Matilda [unknown], Walnut Grove, Tennessee to Isaac Newton Huddle. 10 October 1871., 1 p. (Folder-item 1:1)
      Re: her wedding to Mr. Charles.
    - Letter. James Buchanan, Rural Retreat, Virginia to Isaac Newton Huddle. 6 August 1892., 1 p. (Folder-item 1:2)
      Re: watch he sold to pay Dr. Hobson Clark.
    - Letter. W. W. B. Tilson, Chatham Hill, Virginia to John Huddle. 13 March 1912., 1 p. (Folder-item 1:3)
      Re: request that Huddle pay Ogden Neff for feed.
  - Folder 2. Correspondence - 2008 Addendum. 1868-1876, 8 items.
    - Letter. A. C> M. Earhart, Dayton, Missouri to Isaac Newton Huddle. 9 June 1867., 4 p. (Folder-item 2:1)
      Re: He recounts his journey to Missouri from Bristol, Indiana and his farming endeavors with his brother.
    - Letter. William Dunford, Wythe County, Virginia to Lew Guillion. 18 June 1868., 2 p. (Folder-item 2:2)
      Re: Mrs. Latz agrees to take you now if you will come. Possibly Louisa Guillion, daughter of Major Guillion and ELizabeth H. Gordon Guillion.
    - Letter. Fannie Yonce to Isaac Newton Huddle. 18 June 1868., 2 p. (Folder-item 2:3)
      Re:request that he send photographs of himself.
    - Letter. James H. Matney, Spencer, Indiana to Isaac Newton Huddle. 14 July 1871., 4 p. (Folder-item 2:4)
      Re: farming in Indiana, timber, his work as a plasterer and brick-layer, and John Huddle of Burkes Garden now living in Attica, Indiana.
    - Letter. James H. Matney, Spencer, Indiana to Isaac Newton Huddle. 22 August 1871., 2 p. (Folder-item 2:5)
      Re: weather, corn, and his job constructing a dry goods store in Indianapolis.
    - Letter. Joseph Francis Marion Huddle, Rotherwoood, Hawkins County, TEnnessee to Isaac Newton Huddle. 22 December 1871., 2 p. (Folder-item 2:6)
      Re: Tennessee girls, Will Crigger, James A. Fisher, and David Jones.
    - Letter. Joseph Groseclose, Kingsport, Tennessee to Isaac Newton Huddle. 19 February 1875., 1 p. (Folder-item 2:7)
      Re: financial notes and mild winter.
    - Letter. Gibboney and Son, Wytheville, Virginia to Isaac Newton Huddle. 6 December 1876., 1 p. (Folder-item 2:8)
      Re: account for blasting powder.
  - Folder 3. Correspondence - 2008 Addendum. 1884-1886., 13 items.
    - Letter. W. W. Yost, Wytheville, Virginia to Isaac Newton Huddle. 30 January 1884., 2 p. (Folder-item 3:1)
      Re: lawsuit for debt of Repass.
    - Letter. John P. Sheffey, Marion, Virginia to Isaac Newton Huddle, Rural Retreat, Virginia. 19 March 1884., 1 p. (Folder-item 3:2)
      Re: debt for horse named Rockingham.
    - Letter. John P. Sheffey, Marion, Virginia to Isaac Newton Huddle, Rural Retreat, Virginia. 8 April 1884., 1 p. (Folder-item 3:3)
      Re: claim of J. A. Repass vs. R. M. Williams.
    - Letter. W. Y. Howe to Isaac Newton Huddle. 28 June 1884., 1 p. (Folder-item 3:4)
      Re: payment for Mr. Leonard to buy cow from Mr. Hoofnagle.
    - Postcard. W. W. Yonce, Fremont, Nebraska to Isaac Newton Huddle, Rural Retreat, Virginia. 22 March 1885., postcard. (Folder-item 3:5)
      Re: his move to Nebraska.
    - Letter. W. W. Yonce, Fremont, Nebraska to Isaac Newton Huddle. 2 August 1885., 2 p. (Folder-item 3:6)
      Re: asks him for truth about rumor that a man is at Johns and has a niger yongon. I would ask some of my peopel about hit but I know that tay will knot tell me the truth about hit.
    - Letter. N. B. Studebaker, Charleston, Tennessee to Isaac Newton Huddle. 11 September 1885., 2 p. (Folder-item 3:7)
      Re: cabbage and his school.
    - Letter. W. W. Studebaker, Charleston, Tennessee to Isaac Newton Huddle. 19 September 1885., 4 p. (Folder-item 3:8)
      Re: crates of cabbage, illness of George Catron and Mrs. Catron.
    - Letter. W. W. Yonce, Fremont, Nebraska to Isaac Newton Huddle. 29 September 1885., 4 p. (Folder-item 3:9)
      Re: decision to stay in Nebraska, Charley Baumgardner, John Dutton, Solomon Crockett, his Congregational Church, and cabbage.
    - Postcard. F. A. Yonce, Wytheville, Virginia to Isaac Newton Huddle, Rural Retreat, Virginia. 14 December 1885., postcard. (Folder-item 3:10)
      Re: birthdate of Jacob Tobler and his teaching job.
    - Letter. J. C> Pope, Groses, Smyth County, Virginia to Isaac Newton Huddle. 15 December 1885., 1 p. (Folder-item 3:11)
      Re: inability to pay debt until his leather is ready to be shipped.
    - Letter. J. C. Pope, Groses, Smyth County, Virginia to Isaac Newton Huddle. 30 December 1885., 1 p. (Folder-item 3:12)
      Re: selling corn.
    - Letter. J. C. Pope, Gorses, Smyth County, Virginia to Isaac Newton Huddle. 18 January 1886., 1 p. (Folder-item 3:13)
      Re: selling corn to Mr. Jones and bacon to Mrs. Phillippi.
  - Folder 4. Correspondence - 2008 Addendum - Henry Huddle to Isaac Newton Huddle. 1871-1872., 7 items.
    - Letter. Henry Huddle, Rotherwood, Tennessee to Isaac Newton Huddle. 24 December 1871., 2 p. (Folder-item 4:1)
      Re: fear of living near river, catching a fish as big as his son Jefferson Davis Huddle, Robert Harkrader, the Pawlett account, Steffey School account, James Swacker and cattle, and the old Cassell family farm.
    - Letter. Henry Huddle, Rotherwood, Tennessee to ISaac Newton Huddle. 11 February 1872., 2 p. (Folder-item 4:2)
      Re: cold winter, planting corn, new variety of tomatoes from New York, wax bunch beans and pumpkin seeds.
    - Letter. Henry Huddle, Rotherwood, Tennessee to Isaac Newton Huddle. 10 March 1872., 2 p. (Folder-item 4:3)
      Re: illness of Polly Matilda Etter Huddle, busy time at Kingsport shipping flour and corn. I wish you could have been here for it was a rite smart show to see 4,000 bushels all sacked in 2 bushel sacks.
    - Letter. Henry Huddle, Rotherwood, Tennessee to Isaac Newton Huddle. 31 March 1872., 2 p.; postscript by Polly Huddle. (Folder-item 4:4)
      Re: plans to purchase land, Thomas Creager whom he thinks is a liar and rascal, crop of wheat, oats, corn; weather, health of Ephraim Brown and Benjamin Brown.
    - Letter. Henry Huddle, Rotherwood, Tennessee to Isaac Newton Huddle. 9 APril 1872., 2 p. (Folder-item 4:5)
      Re: sweet potatoes, lettuce, corn, peaches, grass, clover, and the Steffey account.
    - Letter. Henry Huddle, Rotherwood, Tennessee to Isaac Newton Huddle. 19 May 1872., 3 p. (Folder-item 4:6)
      Re: shooting of Hugh Davis, crops of corn, oats, wheat, sweet potatoes, quitting pipe smoking, noise of locusts and frogs being as Farow's Plagues.
    - Letter. Henry Huddle, Rotherwood, Tennessee to Isaac Newton Huddle. 15 August 1872., 2 p. (Folder-item 4:7)
      Re: death of John Tobler, husband of Mary Magdalene Huddle, camp meeting held by black members, catfish weighing 45 pounds.
  - Folder 5. Correspondence - 2008 Addendum - Henry Huddle to Isaac Newton Huddle. 1873-1884, 6 items.
    - Letter. Henry Huddle, Kingsport, Tennessee to Isaac Newton Huddle. 25 January 1873., 2 p. (Folder-item 5:1)
      Re: his new home formerly owned by Rev. Samuel Patton, requests newspaper from David St. Clair, his interest in corn mill.
    - Letter. Henry Huddle, Kingsport, Tennessee to Isaac Newton Huddle. 16 March 1873., 1 p. (Folder-item 5:2)
      Re: apple tree grafts, crop of lettuce, radishes and oats.
    - Letter. Henry Huddle, Kingsport, Tennessee to Isaac Newton Huddle. 4 June 1873., 4 p. (Folder-item 5:3)
      Re: crops, Franklin Dutton; frost that killed peach crop, desire to sell his interest in corn mill jointly owned by David Litz and John Brown.
    - Letter. Henry Huddle, Kingsport, Tennessee to Isaac Newton Huddle. 17 October 1875., 4 p. (Folder-item 5:4)
      Re: diptheria of Ellen Groseclose, fever of Dr. James Vance, death of his horse, and corn mill transaction with David Litz and John Brown.
    - Letter. Henry Huddle, Kingsport, Tennessee to Isaac Newton Huddle. 28 August 1876., 2 p. (Folder-item 5:5)
      Re: crops, supposed insanity of David Staley, corn mill transaction with David Litz and John Brown.
    - Letter. Henry Huddle, Kingsport, Tennessee to Isaac Newton Huddle. 14 January 1884., 2 p. (Folder-item 5:6)
      Re: pneumonia of Alfred Cregar, his old age at 62, postscript by Jefferson Davis Huddle re: hunting and desire to meet girls.
  - Folder 6. Correspondence - 2008 Addendum - JOseph Shannon to Isaac Newton Huddle. 1866-1868., 9 items.
    - Letter. Joseph N. Shannon, Attica, Indiana to Isaac Newton Huddle. 8 April 1866., 3 p. (Folder-item 6:1)
      Re: move to Indiana and lost boxes, and abundant corn crop.
    - Letter. Joseph N. Shannon, Attica, Indiana to Isaac Newton Huddle. 13 May 1866., 2 p. (Folder-item 6:2)
      Re: sick horse, and his father quit teaching school because of illness.
    - Letter. Joseph N. Shannon, Attica, Indiana to Isaac Newton Huddle. 16 December 1866., 2 p. (Folder-item 6:3)
      Re:corn harvest, apple crop, rabbit hunting, teaching career of his father who earns $35.00 monthly at the free school
    - Letter. Joseph N. Shannon, Attica, Indiana to Isaac Newton Huddle. 2 February 1867., 3 p. (Folder-item 6:4)
      Re: cold weather and snow, price of sleighs, rabbit hunting, and local schools.
    - Letter. Joseph Shannon, Attica, Indiana to Isaac Newton Huddle. 23 June 1867., 3 p. (Folder-item 6:5)
      Re: his corn crop, bad wheat crop, and opinion on freedom of former slaves.
    - Letter. Joseph Shannon, Attica, Indiana to Isaac Newton Huddle. 21 August 1867., 4 p. (Folder-item 6:6)
      Re: threshing wheat, corn crp, and his failed attempt to make arrangements for Huddle to send him money through postal service.
    - Letter. Joseph Shannon, Attica, Indiana to Isaac Newton Huddle. 6 December 1867., 3 p. (Folder-item 6:7)
      Re: good corn harvest, local schools, and missing postal money order that Huddle sent.
    - Letter. Joseph Hannon, Attica, Indiana to Isaac Newton Huddle. 19 February 1868., 3 p. (Folder-item 6:8)
      Re: protracted church meetings at Presbyterian and Methodist gatherings, support for George H. Pendleton of Ohio for President.
    - Letter. Joseph Shannon, Attica, Indiana to Isaac Newton Huddle. 19 July 1868., 4 p. (Folder-item 6:9)
      Re: corn crop, drought, wheat harvest, high temperatures, presidential political campaign, Grant is no more worthy of the office than your dog in my view.
  - Folder 7. Correspondence - 2008 Addendum - Joseph Shannon to Isaac Newton Huddle. 1871-1872., 5 items.
    - Letter. Joseph Shannon, Attica, Indiana to Isaac Newton Huddle. 19 February 1871., 6 p. (Folder-item 7:1)
      Re: winter weather, wheat and corn crops, construction of new railroad, engagements in Wythe County, visit of relative to Kansas who purchased land for family.
    - Letter. Joseph Shannon, Attica, Indiana to Isaac Newton Huddle. 2 April 1871., 4 p. (Folder-item 7:2)
      Re: his decision to quit school to farm, marriage of William Dunford, tells Huddle to move west to Kansas.
    - Letter. Joseph Shannon, Attica, Indiana to Isaac Newton Huddle. 16 July 1871., 4 p. (Folder-item 7:3)
      Re: Sunday School lessons, harvesting crops, news from Reuben Repass in Kansas, relocation of John Huddle and Alfred Repass to Attica, Indiana, construction of railroad between his house and barn. We find them very troublesome, six men and three teams are staying with us.
    - Letter. Joseph Shannon, Attica, Indiana to Isaac Newton Huddle. 14 September 1871., 4 p. (Folder-item 7:4)
      Re: prevalent illness of ague in Attica, planting of corn and clover, construction of railroad, John Huddle, and probability of Henry Have returning to Virginia.
    - Letter. Joseph Shannon, Attica, Indiana to Isaac Newton Huddle. 21 January 1872., 4 p. (Folder-item 7:5)
      Re: illness of Tommy Shannon, fear of smallpox in Attica, Indiana, and sleigh riding.
  - Folder 8. Correspondence - 2008 Addendum - Robert Snavely to Isaac Newton Huddle. 1874-1876., 5 items.
    - Letter. Robert Snavely, Virginia Agricultural and Mechanical College, Blacksburg, Virginia to Isaac Newton Huddle. 17 APril 1874., 4 p. (Folder-item 8:1)
      Re: Kimberlin Luthern Church Sunday School, successor to Jonas Groseclose, address of Rev. David F. Bittle, and his opinions on area marriages. I should not be so very much surprised to hear of divorcements as I really think some of the marriages made last fall are rather shabby.
    - Letter. Robert Snavely, Virginia Agricultural and Mechanical College, Blacksburg, Virginia to Isaac Newton Huddle. 14 September 1874., 4 p. (Folder-item 8:2)
      Re: his Latin, Greek, German, chemistry, and mathematics classes; James Lafayette Buck, and new students known as sick rats.
    - Letter. Robert Snavely, Virginia Agricultural and Mechanical College, Blacksburg, Virginia to Isaac Newton Huddle. 8 October 1874., 4 p. (Folder-item 8:3)
      Re:Kimberlin Lutheran Church Sunday School, election of Jacob Snavely to convention, camp meeting, and his concentration on his studies. I never hunt or participate in any sport scarcely as I find the simplest amusement will hinder any one's progress in study.
    - Letter. Robert Snavely, Virginia Agricultural and Mechanical College, Blacksburg, Virginia to Isaac Newton Huddle. 22 March 1875., 4 p. (Folder-item 8:4)
      Re: compatibility with new roommate, new students Guy Brown and Marion Brown, monety stolen from Smyth County student William Davis, and Huddle's debating society.
    - Letter. Robert Snavely, Virginia Agricultural and Mechanical College, Blacksburg, Virginia to Isaac Newton Huddle. 13 April 1876., 6 p. (Folder-item 8:5)
      Re: death of Franklin Dutton, participation in inter-collegiate Virginia oratory society, bad apple crop, and hope to get teaching job at Pleasant Hill School in Smyth County, Virginia.
- Financial Records. 1807-1953, Undated., 22 folders
  - Folder 1. Financial Records - Jonas Huddle Account Book. 1842-1845., 26 p.; written in German.
  - Folder 2. Financial Records - Jonas Huddle Account Book. 1842-1845., 74 p.; 3 loose papers; pages numbered in pencil.
  - Folder 3. Financial Records - Isaac Newton Huddle Account Book. 1893-1894., 8 p.; pencil.
  - Financial Records - Receipts - Henry Huddle. 1807., 1 receipt.
  - Folder 5. Financial Records - Receipts - Jonas Huddle. 1844-1854., 20 receipts.
  - Folder 6. Financial Records - Receipts - Jonas Huddle. 1856-1878, Undated., 11 receipts.
  - Folder 7. Financial Records - Receipts - Isaac Newton Huddle. 1871-1897., 17 receipts.
  - Folder 8. Financial Records - Receipts - Copenbarger Family. 1821-1856., 5 receipts.
  - Folder 9. Financial Records - Receipts - Snavely Family. 1849-1871., 4 receipts.
  - Folder 10. Financial Records - Receipts - Staley Family. 1848-1869, Undated., 23 receipts.
  - Folder 11. Financial Records - Receipts - Miscellaneous. 1830-1953, Undated., 15 receipts.
  - Folder 12. Financial Records - Tax Receipts - Henry Huddle and Jonas Huddle. 1845-1876., 4 items.
  - Folder 13. Financial Records - Tax Receipts - Isaac Newton Huddle. 1870-1898., 14 items.
  - Folder 14. Financial Records - Tax Receipts - Isaac Newton Huddle. 1900-1917., 16 items.
  - Folder 15. Financial Records - Tax Receipts - Miscellaneous. 1845-1891., 6 items.
  - Folder 16. Financial Records - Insurance - Isaac Newton Huddle. 1904., 1 item.
    Policy for house and storage buildings in Black Lick, Virginia from Farmers Mutual Fire Insurance Company.
  - Folder 16. Financial Records - Promissory Note and Bonds. 1832-1857., 7 items.
  - Folder 18. Financial Records - Estate of Adam Snavely, Henry Huddle, Administrator. 1826-1835, Undated., 5 items.
  - Folder 19. Financial Records - Estate of David Musser, Jonas Huddle, Guardian of Heirs - Receipts and Account Statements. 1833-1849, Undated., 16 items.
  - Folder 20. Financial Records - Estate of David Musser, Jonas Huddle, Guardian of Heirs - Receipts and Bonds. 1850-1852., 20 items.
  - Folder 21. Financial Records - Estate of David Musser, Jonas Huddle, Guardian of Heirs - Receipts. 1853-1859, Undated., 18 items.
  - Folder 22. Financial Records - 2008 Addendum. 1800-1918., 6 items.
- Series III. Land Records. 1796-1896, Undated., 2 folders.
  Folder 1 contains 10 deeds dating from 1796 to 1896; Folder 2 contains surveys, 1826 and undated. Folder 3 contains deeds from the 2008 Addendum, dating 1809 to 1912.
- Series IV. Education Records. 1812-1882, Undated., 6 folders.
  Folder 1 contains a writing notebook of James E. Poe ca. 1812; Folder 2 and Folder 3 contain arithmetic notebooks dating 1819 of Jonas Huddle; Folder 4 contains an arithmetic notebook dating from 1824-1825 of JOnas Huddle. Folder 5 contains a book of Isaac Newton Huddles on arithmetic entitled Caldwell's Practical Arithmetic. Folder 6 contains compositions by Isaac Newton Huddle.
- Series V. Miscellaneous Records. 1868-1871, Undated., 2 folders.
  Folder 1 contains brochures for various products, a schedule for the Louisville, St. Louis and Chicago Railroad, a hand-drawn map of Virginia, an article by Jonas Huddle on the Sluss family massacre, and a poem. Folder 2, from the 2008 Addendum, contains two poems and a summons to Daniel Fulkner dated 1802.
- Series VI. Black Lick Township Records. 1870-1875., 41 folders.
  Folders 1 through Folder 10contain claims Black Lick residents filed for services rendered to the Township Board. Although most claims involved payment due for road maintenance, residents who built coffins, provided room and board, and gave medical care also filed claims. Boar dmembers reviewed and paid claims at most of their regular meetings. Claims are arranged alphabetically and date from 1870 to 1874.
  Folder 11 through Folder 20 contain tax receipts dating 1871 to 1873 for Black Lick Township residents. The Township levied an 11% tax on eery $100 value of real estate and personal property; receipts are alphabetical by surname.